# Hau-Hung Yang

Department of Psychology, National Taiwan University, Taipei, TAIWAN Phone: +886-9-76165828 E-mail: r09227103@ntu.edu.tw

### **PERSONAL PROFILE**

Highly motivated M.S. student in Psychology with expertise in Statistics and Quantitative Psychology. Research assistant with 3 years of experiences analyzing behavior and fMRI data. Overall GPA 4.12 in undergraduate. Seeking new models for ordinal scale data and appropriate hypothesis testing procedures for ordered restrictive inferences.

# **EDUCATION**

2020-present M.S. in Psychology, National Taiwan University, Taipei, Taiwan

Last year GPA: 4.18 Relevant courses:

Advanced Statistical Inference (GPA: 4.3, Department of

Mathematics), Experimental Design (GPA: 4.3), Introduction to

Stochastic Modeling (GPA: 4.3)

2016-2020 B.S. in Psychology, National Taiwan University, Taipei, Taiwan

Overall GPA: 4.12

Awards: ranked 3<sup>rd</sup> in sixth semester

# **RESEARCH EXPERIENCE**

#### Research Assistant

2020-Present Project: Analysis of Cognitive Structures Underlying Financial Behavior Department of Psychology, National Taiwan University

- Search and review related literature and collected questionnaire of bias in financial behaviors
- Use exploratory factor analysis to find the latent structure behind variance covariance matrix of financial bias questionnaire
- Make statistical inferences and interpretations of the latent variables of financial bias

# **RESEARCH EXPERIENCE (CONTINUED)**

2018-2020 Project: From Mind Reading to Mind Sharing: A Study on Neural Correlates of Cognitive and Affective Theory of Mind and Their Applications to Salesforce Enhancement

Department of International Business, National Taiwan University

- Taught new team members preprocessing and analysis of behavior data
- Mentored new team members in preprocessing and statistical analysis of neuroimaging data
- Reviewed and reported related literature and journal articles, including synchronization, structural equation modeling, and theory of mind

2017-2020 Project: Coalition without Trust: The Intra-Brain Connectivity and
Inter-Brain Synchronization of Herd Behaviors in an Economic Bubble
Game

Department of International Business, National Taiwan University

- Explored the possible mechanism behind behavior for the use of visualization of data and descriptive statistics
- Constructed probability models and appropriate hypothesis tests to make statistical inferences for the economic bubble game
- Preprocessed the fMRI data and construct a model to explain brain activity based on behavior data
- Mentored new team members in preprocessing and statistical analysis of neuroimaging data
- Taught new team members preprocessing and analysis of behavior data
- Reviewed and reported related literature and journal articles, including diffusion model, reinforcement learning, prospect theory, and behavioral economics

#### **RESEARCH INTERESTS**

- Use drift diffusion model and related sequential sampling models for choice behavior
- Incorporate response confidence (or response time) into the stochastic approximation algorithm to gain more efficient estimation of threshold in psychophysical experiments
- Decision making and preferences in behavioral economics

# **TEACHING EXPERIENCE**

2020-2021 Teaching Assistant, Statistics in Psychology and Education Department of Psychology, National Taiwan University

- Created and graded course assignments, including R programming practice and statistical inferences
- Graded midterm and final exam
- Taught R programming in hand-on course sections
   Teaching Assistant. Statistics in Psychology and Education

2019-2020 Teaching Assistant, Statistics in Psychology and Education

Department of Psychology, National Taiwan University

- Created and graded course assignments, including R programming practice and statistical inferences
- Created and graded midterm and final exam
- Taught R programming in hand-on course sections